The next exercise that we're going to do is called seal puppy.
So, take one hand and wrap it through one leg.
The other hand to wrap it through the other.
Clap your feet three times together, and just like on rolling like a ball, inhale to go back, clap your feet three times and come up on the exhale and clap your feet.
Again, do not let yourself roll so far forward that your feet touch.
But try to stop in the beginning position.
Clap your feet again, initiate with the pelvic tilt.
Go back clap and come up.
You can vary the intensity of the exercise by pulling your feet in closer to you or by stretching them out farther away.
This just like rolling like a ball is an excellent massage for your spine.